[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Wild Bloom]
[وايلد بلوم]
[Episode 16]
[الحلقة 16]
Mom, I just got divorced.
أمي ، لقد طلقت للتو.
This is also a second marriage for both of us.
هذا أيضًا زواج ثانٍ لكلينا.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
I told you not to do it,
قلت لك لا تفعل ذلك ،
but you insisted on doing it.
لكنك أصررت على فعل ذلك.
Now, this is the result.
الآن ، هذه هي النتيجة.
Feng Yu.
فنغ يو.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
It is not a good omen.
إنه ليس فأل خير.
A wedding.
حفل زفاف.
Don't take it to heart.
لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد.
Right?
حق؟
It's just a wedding.
إنه مجرد حفل زفاف.
But no matter how much you drink,
ولكن بغض النظر عن مقدار ما تشربه ،
I have to be honest with you.
يجب أن أكون صادقا معك.
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
Bao'er and your mother-in-law
باور وحماتك
are not easygoing.
ليست بسيطة.
You start to live together after you get married.
تبدأ في العيش معًا بعد الزواج.
But you have to take the initiative
لكن عليك أن تأخذ زمام المبادرة
into your own hands.
بين يديك.
You used to have a backbone.
اعتدت أن يكون لديك عمود فقري.
Now the backbone...
الآن العمود الفقري ...
You know what I mean, right?
أنت تعرف ما أعنيه الصحيح؟
It's up to you.
الأمر متروك لك.
Only the housekeeper knows how high the living cost can be.
فقط مدبرة المنزل تعرف مدى ارتفاع تكلفة المعيشة.
So young.
صغير جدا.
Do you think she can handle it well?
هل تعتقد أنها تستطيع التعامل معها بشكل جيد؟
Can she be counted on?
هل يمكن الاعتماد عليها؟
Don't lose both people and your wealth.
لا تخسر كلاً من الناس وثروتك.
If you lose the factory,
إذا فقدت المصنع ،
your family will be gone too.
ستزول عائلتك أيضًا.
That's not a nice thing to say.
هذا ليس شيئًا لطيفًا أن أقوله.
But you have to take it to heart.
لكن عليك أن تأخذها على محمل الجد.
For your own sake, do you know that?
لمصلحتك ، هل تعرف ذلك؟
Feng.
فنغ.
Mr. Wu is talking about the problem of
السيد وو يتحدث عن مشكلة
who is truly in charge of the household
من هو المسؤول حقًا عن الأسرة
in the future.
فى المستقبل.
Look, you married before.
انظر ، لقد تزوجت من قبل.
She has never been married.
لم يكن متزوجة.
You know how life is after marriage.
أنت تعرف كيف تكون الحياة بعد الزواج.
Does she know?
هل هي تعلم؟
Mr. Wu just said
قال السيد وو للتو
she's still a child. What does she know?
لا تزال طفلة.  ماذا تعرف؟
So...
لذا...
Enough.
كافية.
It's his family business.
إنه عمل عائلته.
Why are you guys meddling with it?
لماذا تتدخلون في ذلك يا رفاق؟
As for who is in charge of their family,
أما من يتولى أسرهم ،
let Feng discuss it with his family members.
دع فنغ يناقشها مع أفراد عائلته.
I like listening to Miss Xu.
أحب الاستماع إلى الآنسة شو.
Every word makes sense.
كل كلمة لها معنى.
This reminds me of our steel mill.
هذا يذكرني بمصنع الصلب لدينا.
From a small home
من منزل صغير
to a big factory,
لمصنع كبير ،
we all need a backbone, right?
نحن جميعا بحاجة إلى عمود فقري ، أليس كذلك؟
We all need a head of the house.
نحن جميعا بحاجة الى رئيس للمنزل.
I still remember
مازلت اتذكر
what Miss Xu said that night.
ما قالته الآنسة شو في تلك الليلة.
I was very touched.
لقد تأثرت جدا.
She said the merchants in Binhai
فقالت التجار في بنهاي
should not only follow the rules
يجب ألا تتبع القواعد فقط
but also value friendship.
ولكن أيضا قيمة الصداقة.
Miss Xu,
ملكة جمال شو ،
it's time for you to show your loyalty.
حان الوقت لإظهار ولائك.
Where is friendship?
اين الصداقة
Stop talking.
توقف عن الكلام.
Take a rest.
خذ راحة.
All right, let's not talk about other things.
حسنًا ، دعنا لا نتحدث عن أشياء أخرى.
Today, in front of everyone,
اليوم أمام الجميع
in front of so many people.
أمام الكثير من الناس.
Miss Xu, let me ask you something.
آنسة شو ، اسمح لي أن أسألك شيئًا.
Can we continue to work together?
هل يمكننا الاستمرار في العمل معًا؟
Just like what Dong did that night.
تمامًا مثل ما فعله دونغ في تلك الليلة.
Tell me honestly.
قل لي بصراحة.
Don't hold back.
لا تتراجع.
You can say anything, good or bad.
يمكنك أن تقول أي شيء ، جيد أو سيئ.
At least let us know
على الأقل دعنا نعرف
whether you are willing to
ما إذا كنت على استعداد لذلك
cooperate with us or not.
تعاون معنا أم لا.
OK.
نعم.
Since you want me to be honest,
بما أنك تريدني أن أكون صادقًا ،
I'll say it.
سأقولها.
Okay.
تمام.
Yes, it's good to work together.
نعم ، من الجيد العمل معًا.
But if we work together,
ولكن إذا عملنا معًا ،
we should respect each other.
يجب أن نحترم بعضنا البعض.
Is the ratio you gave
هي النسبة التي أعطيتها
appropriate?
ملائم؟
Yes, I've come this far as a waste collector.
نعم ، لقد وصلت إلى هذا الحد بصفتي جامع نفايات.
All of you
كلكم
must be upset.
يجب أن ينزعج.
I understand.
أفهم.
But I also
ولكن أنا أيضا
work through my own efforts.
العمل من خلال جهودي الخاصة.
I travelled the route to purchase the steel myself.
سافرت في الطريق لشراء الفولاذ بنفسي.
Even the source from the Heihai
حتى المصدر من هايهاي
I strive to make it accessible too.
أنا أبذل قصارى جهدي لجعله متاحًا أيضًا.
Ask yourself.
اسال نفسك.
Have I ever made any money without you?
هل جنيت أي أموال بدونك؟
Have I ever kept all the profits to myself? Have I ever been selfish?
هل احتفظت بكل الأرباح لنفسي؟  هل سبق لي أن كنت أنانيًا؟
How much did you earn from me?
كم جنيت مني؟
Now you don't want me to take the management rights.
الآن أنت لا تريد مني أن آخذ حقوق الإدارة.
Look down on me.
تطل على لي.
Mr. Qiu, your factory,
السيد كيو ، المصنع الخاص بك ،
in the past year,
في العام الماضي ،
would have been gone long ago without me.
كان قد ذهب منذ فترة طويلة بدوني.
Right?
حق؟
I don't ask for your gratitude.
أنا لا أطلب امتنانك.
But I hope for
لكني آمل
a little respect.
قليل من الاحترام.
She has never kept all the profits to herself.
لم تحتفظ بكل الأرباح لنفسها.
She has never been selfish.
لم تكن أبدا أنانية.
I can guarantee that.
يمكنني أن أضمن ذلك.
I told you not to talk.
قلت لك لا تتكلم.
Take a break.
خذ استراحة.
Xu,
شو ،
we're not ungrateful.
نحن لسنا جاحدين.
Judging from what you said just now,
انطلاقا مما قلته للتو ،
we should thank
يجب أن نشكر
for your kindness.
لطيبتك.
When you went abroad to import steel scrap,
عندما ذهبت إلى الخارج لاستيراد خردة الصلب ،
did we
هل فعلنا
lend you a hand?
مد يد العون لك؟
We knew you had no money,
كنا نعلم أنه ليس لديك نقود ،
but still took you there.
ولكن لا يزال يأخذك إلى هناك.
And you should remember
وعليك أن تتذكر
when you couldn't pay the deposit.
عندما لا تستطيع دفع الوديعة.
Did I say that?
هل قلت ذلك؟
I said I'm your big brother.
قلت أنا أخوك الأكبر.
I'll pay the deposit for you.
سأدفع الوديعة لك.
The truth, right?
الحقيقة ، أليس كذلك؟
If we're talking about gratitude
إذا كنا نتحدث عن الامتنان
we should start from the beginning.
يجب أن نبدأ من البداية.
It's not necessary to start from the beginning.
ليس من الضروري أن تبدأ من البداية.
You are just being dominant with your words.
أنت فقط تهيمن على كلماتك.
You stand on the moral high ground
أنت تقف على أرضية أخلاقية عالية
and you earn all the profit.
وستكسب كل الأرباح.
In the end, I'm the guilty party.
في النهاية ، أنا الطرف المذنب.
You all despise me from the bottom of your hearts.
كلكم تحتقرونني من أعماق قلوبكم.
Now you're telling me about friendship.
أنت الآن تخبرني عن الصداقة.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
ألا تشعر بالحرج؟
You need to earn the respect yourself.
عليك أن تكسب الاحترام بنفسك.
Yes, you have to get face yourself.
نعم ، عليك أن تواجه نفسك.
Xu Banxia, who do you think you are?
Xu Banxia ، من تعتقد نفسك؟
Didn't we show you dignity?
ألم نظهر لك كرامتك؟
Didn't we show you respect?
ألم نظهر لك الاحترام؟
You came to the dinner.
أتيت إلى العشاء.
I even picked you up personally at the door.
حتى أنني التقطتك شخصيًا عند الباب.
What else do you want me to do?
ماذا تريد مني أن أفعل؟
I really want to hold a mirror
أنا حقا أريد أن أمسك مرآة
and show you
ويظهر لك
how arrogant you are.
كم أنت مغرور.
Who do you think we are?
الذين رأيك نحن؟
Your followers, your boys.
أتباعك ، أولادك.
Your minions.
أتباعك.
You're so funny.
أنت مضحك جدا.
Well, since we've come to this point,
حسنًا ، منذ أن وصلنا إلى هذه النقطة ،
I'll make a decision today.
سوف أتخذ قرار اليوم.
I won't cooperate with you
لن أتعاون معك
on the sources of imported steel scrap.
على مصادر خردة الصلب المستوردة.
If you need my storage yard in the future,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى ساحة التخزين الخاصة بي في المستقبل ،
you're always welcome.
أنت مرحب بك دائما.
The price is still the same as that of friends and family.
السعر لا يزال هو نفسه مثل الأصدقاء والعائلة.
I wish you all a prosperous business
أتمنى لكم جميعا عمل مزدهر
and prosperous fortune in the days ahead.
وثروة مزدهرة في الأيام المقبلة.
Did you see that?
هل رأيت ذلك؟
You all don't understand me.
كلكم لا تفهموني.
No one understands me.
لا أحد يفهمني.
Do you think I've gone too far today?
هل تعتقد أنني ذهبت بعيدا جدا اليوم؟
Yes.
نعم.
Did you see how those old guys
هل رأيت كيف هؤلاء الرجال الكبار
reprimanded me
وبخني
at the dinner table?
على طاولة العشاء؟
They just look down on me.
هم فقط ينظرون إلي بازدراء.
Today, I want them to know
اليوم ، أريدهم أن يعرفوا
who is in charge and who is the boss.
من هو المسؤول ومن هو الرئيس.
Without the sources of imported steel scrap,
بدون مصادر خردة الحديد المستوردة ،
they are nothing.
هم لا شيء.
So have you vented your anger?
فهل تنفست عن غضبك؟
They should know today
يجب أن يعرفوا اليوم
who the boss is.
من هو الرئيس.
And then?
وثم؟
Did you ever wonder if they would have looked down on you
هل تساءلت يومًا ما إذا كانوا سينظرون إليك باستخفاف
two years ago?
منذ عامين؟
They couldn't see you.
لم يتمكنوا من رؤيتك.
Yes.
نعم.
They scolded you
لقد وبخوك
at the dinner table today
على مائدة العشاء اليوم
because they were afraid of you.
لأنهم كانوا خائفين منك.
'Cause you make them
لأنك تصنعهم
feel threatened.
تشعر بأنها مهددة.
'Cause you are strong enough.
لأنك قوي بما فيه الكفاية.
I think at this moment
أعتقد في هذه اللحظة
we should sit down and talk.
يجب أن نجلس ونتحدث.
Talk nicely.
تحدث بلطف.
Only then,
حينها فقط،
the steel mill can be more secure.
يمكن أن تكون مطحنة الصلب أكثر أمانًا.
As the saying goes,
على رأي القول،
there are only permanent interests in business,
لا يوجد سوى مصالح دائمة في الأعمال التجارية ،
There are no permanent enemies.
لا يوجد أعداء دائمون.
Of course,
بالطبع،
we don't have friends forever.
ليس لدينا أصدقاء إلى الأبد.
Are you going to be that kind of person?
هل ستكون هذا النوع من الأشخاص؟
What kind of person?
أي نوع من الأشخاص؟
Well,
نحن سوف،
a scary person.
شخص مخيف.
Are you afraid of me?
هل أنت خائف مني؟
I...
أنا...
It depends.
هذا يعتمد.
When?
متى؟
Do you want to ask
هل تريد ان تسأل
is it this moment?
هل هي هذه اللحظة
Yes.
نعم.
I'm asking you
أنا أسألك
are you afraid of me now?
هل انت خائف مني الان
Who is so ignorant?
من هذا الجهل؟
Hello, boss.
مرحبا يا رئيس.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Something happened.
شيء ما حصل.
Chen was taken away by the police.
تم أخذ تشين من قبل الشرطة.
Find someone to ask what happened.
ابحث عن شخص ما لتسأل عما حدث.
Yes.
نعم.
Yes, it's ours.
نعم ، إنها لنا.
Okay, I got it.
حسنا حصلت عليه.
Thank you and sorry for the trouble.
شكرا لك وآسف على المتاعب.
Okay.
تمام.
Okay, bye.
حسنًا ، إلى اللقاء.
There are reports of weapons possession and arms smuggling
هناك تقارير عن حيازة أسلحة وتهريب أسلحة
in your storage yard.
في ساحة التخزين الخاصة بك.
The provincial inspector came down for a raid.
نزل مفتش المقاطعة لشن غارة.
Arms smuggling.
تهريب الأسلحة.
Are you kidding?
هل تمزح؟
I've got all the paperwork here.
لدي كل الأعمال الورقية هنا.
Who reported it?
من أبلغ عنها؟
Anonymous.
مجهول.
It is true that in the past few years,
صحيح أنه في السنوات القليلة الماضية ،
some foreign dealers did
فعل بعض التجار الأجانب
pass away the sham as the genuine.
تزول الوهمية على أنها حقيقية.
The country is quite strict about this.
البلد صارم للغاية بشأن هذا الأمر.
Most importantly, these foreigners
الأهم من ذلك ، هؤلاء الأجانب
are too lazy to turn these large pieces of steel
كسالى جدا لقلب هذه القطع الكبيرة من الفولاذ
into scrap.
في الخردة.
You didn't go to the warehouse
لم تذهب إلى المستودع
during the recent purchase of goods, did you?
خلال عملية الشراء الأخيرة للسلع ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, Chen was in charge of it.
نعم ، كان تشين مسؤولاً عنها.
When I went to the storage yard,
عندما ذهبت إلى ساحة التخزين ،
I found
وجدت
some well-preserved grenades.
بعض القنابل اليدوية المحفوظة جيدًا.
I was wondering
كنت أتساءل
if these things can function well
إذا كانت هذه الأشياء يمكن أن تعمل بشكل جيد
after replacing some parts.
بعد استبدال بعض الأجزاء.
And those tanks.
وتلك الدبابات.
Parking there in a row.
وقوف السيارات هناك على التوالي.
It's quite impressive.
إنه أمر مثير للإعجاب.
The boundary is also vague.
كما أن الحدود غامضة.
Look.
نظرة.
We are legal.
نحن قانونيون.
Yes, it's legal.
نعم ، هذا قانوني.
On the customs clearance documents,
على وثائق التخليص الجمركي ،
it states steel scrap.
تنص على خردة الصلب.
Then as for the weapons in the warehouse
ثم بالنسبة للأسلحة في المستودع
How should we define them?
كيف يجب أن نحددها؟
Should we define it as steel scrap
هل يجب أن نعرّفها بأنها خردة فولاذية
or arms?
أو السلاح؟
It's a toss-up.
إنها إهمال.
What about Chen? What did they say?
ماذا عن تشين؟  ماذا قالوا؟
Chen, they said he isn't under detention.
تشين ، قالوا إنه ليس رهن الاحتجاز.
Just to assist in the investigation.
فقط للمساعدة في التحقيق.
The key is you.
المفتاح هو أنت.
They need you to go
يريدونك أن تذهب
to the police station tomorrow.
إلى مركز الشرطة غدا.
OK.
نعم.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
This is...
هذا هو...
a tank. A main battle tank in the past.
دبابة.  دبابة قتال رئيسية في الماضي.
It weighs 32 tons normally.
يزن 32 طنًا في المعتاد.
They sold as 26 tons.
باعوا 26 طنا.
'Cause there are many belts and instruments
لأن هناك الكثير من الأحزمة والأدوات
made of alloy.
مصنوعة من سبيكة.
They are useless even when they are melted.
لا فائدة منها حتى عندما تذوب.
You don't need to talk about the business with me.
لست بحاجة للتحدث معي عن العمل.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Why are these all weapons?
لماذا كل هذه الأسلحة؟
I imported them as steel scrap in Heihai.
لقد قمت باستيرادها كخردة فولاذية في Heihai.
I follow the national guide.
أنا أتبع الدليل الوطني.
Not all of them are weapons.
ليس كل منهم أسلحة.
The other day I also imported some
في اليوم الآخر ، قمت أيضًا باستيراد بعض
large-sized agricultural harvesters.
حصادات زراعية كبيرة الحجم.
Don't you need to write clearly
لا تحتاج إلى الكتابة بوضوح
in your customs declaration documents?
في وثائق البيان الجمركي الخاص بك؟
Can I take a look at the letter of accusation?
هل يمكنني إلقاء نظرة على خطاب الاتهام؟
Do you think you can read it just because you want to?
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنك قراءته لمجرد أنك تريد ذلك؟
Answer me properly.
أجبني بشكل صحيح.
OK.
نعم.
I've always been in the junk business.
لقد كنت دائما في الأعمال غير المرغوب فيها.
For example, that waste paper.
على سبيل المثال ، تلك النفايات الورقية.
It may be a book,
قد يكون كتابًا ،
or newspaper.
او جريدة.
Whatever it is,
مهما تكن،
it will eventually be thrown into the pool of paper making
سيتم إلقاؤه في نهاية المطاف في بركة صناعة الورق
and turn into paper pulps.
وتتحول إلى عجينة ورق.
It's the same with steel scrap.
إنه نفس الشيء مع خردة الفولاذ.
My previous sales records are here.
سجلات مبيعاتي السابقة هنا.
Why don't you check if
لماذا لا تتحقق مما إذا كان
somebody bought it
شخص ما اشتراه
for steel making
لصناعة الصلب
or to start a war?
أو لبدء حرب؟
For instance, someone hurts others with a kitchen knife.
على سبيل المثال ، شخص يؤذي الآخرين بسكين المطبخ.
The kitchen knife seller is not guilty.
بائع سكاكين المطبخ غير مذنب.
It's just a kitchen utensil.
إنها مجرد أواني مطبخ.
Fine.
بخير.
You don't have to teach us the law.
ليس عليك أن تعلمنا القانون.
We'll give you an answer whether you're guilty or not.
سنقدم لك إجابة سواء كنت مذنبا أم لا.
Then what are these?
ثم ما هؤلاء؟
K-Katyusha.
K- كاتيوشا.
What? I didn't hear it.
ماذا؟  لم أسمعه.
Katyusha.
كاتيوشا.
It's a multiple rocket launcher.
إنها قاذفة صواريخ متعددة.
Isn't there a song?
أليست هناك أغنية؟
[When pear blossoms across the cliff]
[عندما تزهر الكمثرى عبر الجرف]
[A gauze floats on the river]
[شاش يطفو على النهر]
[Katyusha]
[كاتيوشا]
Your company's account books and purchase orders
دفاتر حسابات شركتك وأوامر الشراء
are now investigated and collected as evidence.
يتم الآن التحقيق فيها وجمعها كدليل.
During the investigation,
أثناء التحقيق ،
your company's headquarters
مقر شركتك
and other subsidiaries
والشركات التابعة الأخرى
are not allowed to operate normally.
لا يسمح لها بالعمل بشكل طبيعي.
The funds in your company's account
الأموال في حساب شركتك
will also be temporarily frozen.
سيتم أيضًا تجميدها مؤقتًا.
But it is not yet determined.
لكنها لم تحدد بعد.
Why don't we discuss it again?
لماذا لا نناقشها مرة أخرى؟
Give us some time.
امنحنا بعض الوقت.
It is up to the doer to undo the knot.
الأمر متروك للفاعل لفك العقدة.
You should know
يجب ان تعرف
better than us, right?
افضل منا صحيح؟
Mr. Wu.
السيد.  وو.
Mr. Zhao.
السيد تشاو.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
What happened between us is behind us.
ما حدث بيننا وراءنا.
Why can't we talk over the phone?
لماذا لا نستطيع التحدث عبر الهاتف؟
-Sit. -You make it so formal.
-يجلس.  -أنت تجعله رسميًا جدًا.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
I'll sit.
سأجلس.
This is a big deal after all.
هذه صفقة كبيرة بعد كل شيء.
It concerns everyone's interests.
يتعلق بمصالح الجميع.
So,
لذا،
I'd better tell you in person.
من الأفضل أن أخبرك شخصيًا.
Do you know that the storage yard is closed?
هل تعلم أن ساحة التخزين مغلقة؟
Everyone knows.
الجميع يعلم.
I have goods in there too.
لدي بضائع هناك أيضًا.
Our company was reported
تم الإبلاغ عن شركتنا
that we smuggled arms.
بأننا قمنا بتهريب الأسلحة.
Customs and police
الجمارك والشرطة
Even the army was alarmed.
حتى الجيش انزعج.
What a big deal.
يا لها من صفقة كبيرة.
Now we're waiting for the evaluation.
الآن نحن في انتظار التقييم.
Seriously?
بشكل جاد؟
Didn't you import the remaining steel scrap in World War II?
ألم تستورد ما تبقى من خردة الصلب في الحرب العالمية الثانية؟
Besides, you didn't import
علاوة على ذلك ، أنت لم تستورد
guns and bullets.
البنادق والرصاص.
I think it's fine.
أعتقد أنه بخير.
The country will find out soon.
سيكتشف البلد قريبا.
Yes.
نعم.
I believe
أعتقد
the government will find out soon.
ستكتشف الحكومة ذلك قريبًا.
But if the company's credit is questioned,
ولكن إذا تم التشكيك في ائتمان الشركة ،
the account will be blocked.
سيتم حظر الحساب.
If we continue to delay,
إذا واصلنا التأخير ،
we won't be able to participate in the bidding of No.2 Steel.
لن نتمكن من المشاركة في العطاء رقم 2 للصلب.
I just think the timing
أنا فقط أفكر في التوقيت
is too coincidental.
من قبيل الصدفة.
Mr. Wu,
السيد.  وو ،
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Are you suspecting me?
هل تشك بي؟
Foreigner, you suspect me?
أجنبي ، هل تشك بي؟
Mr. Wu, take it easy.
السيد وو ، خذ الأمور ببساطة.
Since it's such a big deal,
نظرًا لأنها صفقة كبيرة ،
it is reasonable
هذا معقول
if I think further a bit, right?
إذا فكرت أكثر قليلاً ، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Zhao, let me put it this way.
السيد تشاو ، اسمحوا لي أن أضعها على هذا النحو.
I transferred from the army.
لقد انتقلت من الجيش.
I got two sets of clothes and one blanket.
حصلت على مجموعتين من الملابس وبطانية واحدة.
I was assigned to be a captain in a transportation company.
تم تكليفي بأن أكون نقيبًا في شركة نقل.
I worked day and night. Not much money I earned by then.
عملت ليلا ونهارا.  لم أكسب الكثير من المال بحلول ذلك الوقت.
But I received a bunch of letters of complaints.
لكنني تلقيت مجموعة من رسائل الشكاوى.
I hate people who stab me in the back.
أكره الناس الذين يطعنونني في ظهري.
That's why I quit.
لهذا السبب استقلت.
I'm a bad-tempered person,
أنا شخص سيء المزاج ،
but I have a good character.
لكن لدي شخصية جيدة.
I earn money with fair and square.
أكسب المال مع عادل ومربع.
I don't need to play dirty
لست بحاجة للعب القذرة
for my business.
لعملي.
Mr. Wu,
السيد.  وو ،
since you've said so,
منذ أن قلت ذلك ،
I know
أنا أعرف
who did this.
من فعل هذا.
There's one more thing.
هناك شيء واحد أكثر.
I think only Mr. Wu can
أعتقد أن السيد وو فقط يمكنه ذلك
handle it.
التعامل معها.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
Miss Xu and Mr. Qiu...
ملكة جمال شو والسيد كيو ...
Mr. Wu. You need to attend to the matter personally.
السيد وو.  أنت بحاجة إلى الاهتمام بهذه المسألة شخصيًا.
Talk to Mr. Qiu.
تحدث إلى السيد كيو.
We can't keep the storage yard closed forever.
لا يمكننا إبقاء ساحة التخزين مغلقة إلى الأبد.
Mr. Zhao, I'll be honest with you.
سيد تشاو ، سأكون صادقًا معك.
You heard it.
انت سمعت ذلك.
Xu Banxia means that
Xu Banxia يعني ذلك
she won't let me take part in
لن تسمح لي بالمشاركة
the steel scrap business anymore.
تجارة خردة الصلب بعد الآن.
Now the storage yard is closed.
الآن ساحة التخزين مغلقة.
What do you want me to do?
ماذا تريدني ان افعل؟
By the way,
على فكرة،
the conflict between Xu Banxia and Qiu Bizheng
الصراع بين Xu Banxia و Qiu Bizheng
is not something in a short period.
ليس شيئًا في فترة قصيرة.
I don't want to get involved in such things.
لا أريد التورط في مثل هذه الأشياء.
Mr. Wu, I'm here today with sincerity.
السيد وو ، أنا هنا اليوم بصدق.
Let me make a statement.
اسمحوا لي أن أدلي ببيان.
In Binhai,
في بينهاى ،
the most prosperous company
الشركة الأكثر ازدهارًا
is Banxia Steel International Trading Co., Ltd.
هي شركة Banxia Steel International Trading Co.، Ltd.
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
no matter which company we join
بغض النظر عن الشركة التي ننضم إليها
to bid for the No.2 Steel,
لتقديم عطاءات للحصول على رقم 2 للصلب ،
the company will have no worries
الشركة لن تقلق
about their finance.
حول تمويلهم.
So with the strength of our company,
وبقوة شركتنا ،
didn't you give us too little before?
ألم تعطينا القليل من قبل؟
How about you give it a reconsideration?
ما رأيك في إعطائها إعادة نظر؟
You're really rich.
أنت غني حقًا.
Your friendship for so many years
صداقتك لسنوات عديدة
was gone just because of the No.2 Steel.
ذهب فقط بسبب الصلب رقم 2.
It's a pity.
هذا مثير للشفقة.
If you must
إذا توجب عليك
contract the State No.2 Steel,
عقد الدولة رقم 2 للصلب ،
I hope you can guide her a little.
آمل أن تتمكن من إرشادها قليلاً.
Foreigner,
أجنبي،
you don't look like an employee.
لا تبدو كموظف.
Xu Banxia is really lucky.
Xu Banxia محظوظ حقًا.
Do you like her?
هل تحبها؟
Mr. Wu, when you take money from someone, you should be loyal to them.
سيد وو ، عندما تأخذ المال من شخص ما ، يجب أن تكون مخلصًا له.
I understand that.
انا افهم ذلك.
I'm with you on this.
أنا معك في هذا.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine. I didn't sleep well in there.
أنا بخير.  لم أنم جيدًا هناك.
You haven't coughed blood these two days, have you?
لم تسعل دماً في هذين اليومين ، أليس كذلك؟
Fatty is here. Don't talk nonsense.
الدهنية هنا.  لا تتحدث عن هراء.
How should we deal with this?
كيف نتعامل مع هذا؟
Boss will handle it. Leave it.
بوس سيتعامل معها.  اتركه.
-What’s wrong? Why are you coughing? -I’ll drive.
-ما هو الخطأ؟  لماذا تسعل؟  -انا ساقود.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I guess it's just winter.
أعتقد أنه مجرد فصل الشتاء.
I got cold in the storage yard.
شعرت بالبرد في ساحة التخزين.
Bronchitis.
التهاب شعبي.
Come on, let's go to the hospital.
تعال ، دعنا نذهب إلى المستشفى.
I'm fine. I took some medicine there.
أنا بخير.  أخذت بعض الأدوية هناك.
I guess I'm just underdressed.
اعتقد انني فقط underddress.
The air is leaping upward a bit.
الهواء يقفز للأعلى قليلاً.
Well...
نحن سوف...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Chen.
تشين.
Thank you for coming.
شكرا لقدومك.
I'm here to pay you back.
أنا هنا لأرد لك المال.
And the phone.
والهاتف.
The money... is all I have now.
المال ... هو كل ما لدي الآن.
My brother took them all.
اخذهم اخي كلهم
The balance
التوازن
I'll pay you back later.
سأدفع لك لاحقًا.
I've never used the phone.
لم أستخدم الهاتف أبدًا.
I only received a text message from you today.
تلقيت فقط رسالة نصية منك اليوم.
These are all from me.
هذه كلها مني
I was very happy when I gave them to you.
كنت سعيدًا جدًا عندما أعطيتها لك.
I don't want to take back this happiness now.
لا أريد استعادة هذه السعادة الآن.
Chen,
تشين ،
you know that I'm actually a...
أنت تعلم أنني في الواقع ...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
As long as you don't tell me,
ما دمت لا تخبرني ،
you aren't.
أنت لست كذلك.
Sit down for a while.
اجلس لفترة.
Do you like me?
هل أعجبك؟
Don't you like me?
الا تحبني
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
[There is a moment]
[هناك لحظة]
[I think there's no more merriness]
[أعتقد أنه لم يعد هناك مرح]
[In the world]
[في العالم]
[Apart from love and loneliness]
[بصرف النظر عن الحب والوحدة]
[There is a moment]
[هناك لحظة]
Chen, how are you doing?
شين ، كيف حالك؟
[I know that the heart can't hold on to anything anymore]
[أعلم أن القلب لا يستطيع التمسك بأي شيء بعد الآن]
Why are you hospitalized?
لماذا انت في المستشفى؟
I've been in poor health since I was a child.
لقد كنت في حالة صحية سيئة منذ أن كنت طفلاً.
[Nobody is beside me]
[لا أحد بجانبي]
I've been having some trouble lately, and that's it.
أواجه بعض المشاكل مؤخرًا ، وهذا كل شيء.
[Apart from grievance and helplessness]
[بصرف النظر عن التظلم والعجز]
I just need some rest.
أنا فقط بحاجة لبعض الراحة.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
[Life is a mix of stubbornness and frustration]
[الحياة مزيج من العناد والإحباط]
Do you believe in fate?
هل تؤمن بالقدر؟
[Ups and downs]
[صعود وهبوط]
I do.
أفعل.
[The excitement and the uncertainty]
[الإثارة وعدم اليقين]
I didn't believe it at first.
لم أصدق ذلك في البداية.
But now I have to believe.
لكن الآن علي أن أصدق.
[The staccato and the subdued one]
[المتقطع والمهدئ]
[Mighty with sorrow]
[عزيز مع الحزن]
You see.
هل ترى.
[Intense and soft]
[مكثف وناعم]
[Crimson and yellow]
[قرمزي وأصفر]
We both believe in fate.
كلانا يؤمن بالمصير.
We still have something in common.
لا يزال لدينا شيء مشترك.
Mr. Chen, are you feeling better?
السيد تشين ، هل تشعر بتحسن؟
How dare you come here?
كيف تجرؤ على المجيء إلى هنا؟
You're not done yet, aren't you?
لم تنته بعد ، أليس كذلك؟
Wildcat stewed it for you.
قطط طهيها لك.
I spilled it.
أنا سكبته.
Chen, I'm leaving.
تشين ، سأرحل.
No, no, wait a minute.
لا ، لا ، انتظر دقيقة.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
You, get out.
انت اخرج.
No, I really have something to do.
لا ، لدي حقًا ما أفعله.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Go away.
يبتعد.
Chen, take care of yourself.
تشين ، اعتني بنفسك.
Send regards to your two brothers.
أرسل تحياتي إلى شقيقيك.
Do you have any sense?
هل لديك اي معنى؟
Why is she here?
لماذا هل هي هنا؟
She wants money from you.
تريد المال منك.
This is the money she returned.
هذا هو المال الذي عادت.
Is this liar
هل هذا كاذب
so cunning now?
ماكرة جدا الآن؟
Tong Xiaoqi, let me tell you.
تونغ شياو تشي ، دعني أخبرك.
If you dare to call her a liar again.
إذا كنت تجرؤ على تسميتها كاذبة مرة أخرى.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I'll smash you to death.
سأحطمك حتى الموت.
Alright, bring it here.
حسنًا ، أحضره هنا.
Hurry up and eat.
اسرع وتناول الطعام.
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
How long have you been coughing?
منذ متى وأنت تسعل؟
You want me to keep it from others.
تريدني أن أبقيه عن الآخرين.
How much longer can I hide it?
كم من الوقت يمكنني إخفاءه؟
You can't hide it anymore, right?
لا يمكنك إخفاء ذلك بعد الآن ، أليس كذلك؟
It's okay.
حسنا.
We still need to date.
ما زلنا بحاجة حتى الآن.
There's still a beautiful life
لا تزال هناك حياة جميلة
waiting for me to enjoy.
في انتظار الاستمتاع.
I'm hungry. Fill the soup.
أنا جائع.  املأ الحساء.
What are you doing? Can't you stop?
ماذا تفعل؟  لا يمكنك التوقف؟
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
The cooking skills of Wildcat
مهارات الطبخ في Wildcat
look good.
تبدو جيدا.
I'll feed you.
سوف أطعمك.
No, I can't afford it. I can do it myself.
لا ، لا يمكنني تحمله.  أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
OK?
نعم؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Su.
هم انهم.
What happened to Chen?
ماذا حدث لتشن؟
Why did he suddenly faint?
لماذا أغمي عليه فجأة؟
He has two lesions in his lungs.
لديه آفتان في رئتيه.
The area is quite large.
المنطقة كبيرة نوعا ما.
This is also a complication caused by blood diseases.
هذا أيضًا من المضاعفات التي تسببها أمراض الدم.
The blood test indicator is out.
مؤشر فحص الدم خارج.
Very bad.
سيئ جدا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
it's worse than what you imagine.
إنه أسوأ مما تتخيله.
What kind of disease?
أي نوع من المرض؟
Lung cancer. Suspected to be a terminal stage.
سرطان الرئة.  يشتبه في أن تكون مرحلة نهائية.
Lung cancer?
سرطان الرئة؟
He only had blood disease before.
كان يعاني من مرض الدم فقط من قبل.
There's nothing wrong with his lungs.
لا حرج في رئتيه.
Are you sure about your examination?
هل أنت متأكد من فحصك؟
Come and take a look.
وتعالوا نلقي نظرة.
This is a shadow on the lungs.
هذا ظل على الرئتين.
It's a large area.
إنها مساحة كبيرة.
The edge has calcified.
الحافة متكلسة.
This is a shadow on the airway.
هذا ظل على مجرى الهواء.
Obviously, the lungs are infected.
من الواضح أن الرئتين مصابة.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Over the past few years
على مدى السنوات القليلة الماضية
has Chen worked for a long time
هل عمل تشين لفترة طويلة
in a place with air pollution
في مكان به تلوث الهواء
and without any protection?
وبدون أي حماية؟
Chen is weak.
تشين ضعيف.
Moreover, he has a blood disease.
علاوة على ذلك ، فهو مصاب بمرض في الدم.
Long-term fatigue
التعب طويل الأمد
will accelerate this disease
سوف يسرع من هذا المرض
and eventually develop into cancer within a short period.
وفي النهاية يتطور إلى سرطان في غضون فترة قصيرة.
What we're doing now is
ما نفعله الآن هو
to suppress the disease with drugs,
لقمع المرض بالعقاقير ،
then supplement it with chemotherapy.
ثم استكمله بالعلاج الكيميائي.
Because his cancer cells
لأن خلاياه السرطانية
have spread too far.
انتشرت بعيدا جدا.
If we operate rashly,
إذا عملنا بتهور ،
the result will not be satisfactory.
النتيجة لن تكون مرضية.
The result is out. It's nothing serious.
النتيجة خارج.  انها غير جدية.
Just a little weak.
فقط ضعيف قليلا.
How can a man be so weak?
كيف يكون الرجل ضعيفا جدا؟
Also, bronchitis.
أيضا ، التهاب الشعب الهوائية.
You just need to recuperate.
تحتاج فقط إلى التعافي.
I'll ask Su later
سأطلب سو لاحقًا
to prescribe some imported medicine for you.
لوصف لك بعض الأدوية المستوردة.
OK.
نعم.
Since there's nothing else,
بما أنه لا يوجد شيء آخر ،
I don't want to stay here anymore.
لا أريد البقاء هنا بعد الآن.
It's uncomfortable here. I want to go home.
إنه غير مريح هنا.  أريد العودة إلى ديارهم.
Okay, let's go home.
حسنًا ، لنذهب إلى المنزل.
Okay, then I'll pack my things.
حسنًا ، سأحزم أشيائي.
You let Su know about this.
لقد سمحت لـ Su بمعرفة هذا.
[The life is short, joy and sorrow are in chaos]
[الحياة قصيرة والفرح والحزن في فوضى]
[In a blink of an eye, the ship has left the shore]
[في غمضة عين ، غادرت السفينة الشاطئ]
Fatty, we're just steel scrap collectors.
سمين ، نحن مجرد جامعي خردة فولاذية.
That's enough in China.
هذا يكفي في الصين.
[Who knows the happiness is real and fake]
[من يعرف السعادة حقيقية ومزيفة]
Why go abroad
لماذا السفر إلى الخارج
to collect steel?
لجمع الفولاذ؟
4 million, my dear.
4 ملايين يا عزيزتي.
[I have neither regrets nor hate. Life consists of half joy and half sorrow]
[أنا لا أندم ولا أكره.  الحياة تتكون من نصف فرح ونصف حزن]
Where can you get so much money?
من أين يمكنك الحصول على الكثير من المال؟
I put my house up for a mortgage.
أطرح منزلي للحصول على رهن عقاري.
[No matter how deep the regret is]
[بغض النظر عن مدى عمق الأسف]
I take the money
أنا آخذ المال
[It's only half of the life]
[إنها فقط نصف العمر]
they saved in treasury bills and pensions.
ادخروا في أذون الخزانة والمعاشات التقاعدية.
This time it's a complete turnaround.
هذه المرة هو تحول كامل.
[The other half is the temporary moment in front]
[النصف الآخر هو اللحظة المؤقتة التي أمامنا]
After this,
بعد هذا،
I'll go back and get down on my knees in front of them.
سأعود وأركع على ركبتي أمامهم.
[And the eternity behind]
[والخلود وراء]
[From brightness to darkness]
[من السطوع إلى الظلام]
[It is only a part of time]
[إنه جزء من الوقت فقط]
Are we still going north?
هل ما زلنا نتجه شمالا؟
[The rest of the life has limited starts]
[بدايات الحياة محدودة]
Are we still going to buy the steel?
هل ما زلنا نشتري الفولاذ؟
Are we still going to make a comeback?
هل ما زلنا في طريقنا للعودة؟
Are we still going to build the storage yard?
هل ما زلنا في طريقنا لبناء ساحة التخزين؟
[Infinite loop]
[حلقة لا نهائية]
[How many people still pursue perfection?]
[كم عدد الأشخاص الذين ما زالوا يسعون إلى الكمال؟]
[Hanging around at the end of time]
[التسكع في نهاية الوقت]
I've never been in a relationship.
لم أكن في علاقة قط.
And I thought
و أعتقدت
I would never date again.
لن أواعد مرة أخرى.
[How many people do you pray to meet?]
[كم عدد الأشخاص الذين تصلي للقائهم؟]
No matter what I am doing now
لا يهم ما أفعله الآن
[It appears in the sky of the city]
[يظهر في سماء المدينة]
I'll always think of her.
سأفكر بها دائما.
I want to see her all the time
اريد ان اراها طوال الوقت
[No matter how deep the regret is]
[بغض النظر عن مدى عمق الأسف]
Do you think this is affection?
هل تعتقد أن هذا هو المودة؟
[It's only half of the life]
[إنها فقط نصف العمر]
[The other half is the temporary moment in front]
[النصف الآخر هو اللحظة المؤقتة التي أمامنا]
[And the eternity behind]
[والخلود وراء]
[From brightness to darkness]
[من السطوع إلى الظلام]
[It is only a part of time]
[إنه جزء من الوقت فقط]
[The rest of the life has limited starts]
[بدايات الحياة محدودة]
[Infinite loop]
[حلقة لا نهائية]
[No matter how deep the regret is]
[بغض النظر عن مدى عمق الأسف]
[It's only half of the life]
[إنها فقط نصف العمر]
[The other half is the temporary moment in front]
[النصف الآخر هو اللحظة المؤقتة التي أمامنا]
[And the eternity behind]
[والخلود وراء]
[From brightness to darkness]
[من السطوع إلى الظلام]
[It is only a part of time]
[إنه جزء من الوقت فقط]
[The rest of the life has limited starts]
[بدايات الحياة محدودة]
[Infinite loop]
[حلقة لا نهائية]
Boss.
رئيس.
Why are you looking for me?
لماذا تبحث عني؟
Chen's girlfriend.
صديقة تشين.
What's her name?
ما أسمها؟
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
She's a marriage scammer.
إنها محتالة زواج.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
She's a liar.
إنها كاذبة.
Chen didn't want you to worry,
تشن لا يريدك أن تقلق ،
so he didn't let me tell you.
لذلك لم يسمح لي أن أخبرك.
And that's why I didn't tell you.
ولهذا لم أخبرك.
Chen is stupid and stubborn.
تشين غبي وعنيد.
He knew it was a marriage scam,
كان يعلم أنها كانت خدعة زواج ،
but still
لكن مازال
spent so much money and treated her so well.
أنفقت الكثير من المال وعاملتها بشكل جيد.
Do you know where she is?
هل تعلم اين هي؟
Can we find her?
ممكن نجدها؟
Why?
لماذا ا؟
I'm just asking if you still know her whereabouts.
أنا فقط أسأل إذا كنت لا تزال تعرف مكان وجودها.
I hit her two days ago.
لقد ضربتها منذ يومين.
I guess she went somewhere else.
أعتقد أنها ذهبت إلى مكان آخر.
Where did she go?
إلى أين ذهبت؟
We must find her today.
يجب أن نجدها اليوم.
No, she's just a liar.
لا ، إنها مجرد كاذبة.
Why are you looking for her?
لماذا تبحث عنها؟
Chen likes her.
تشن تحبها.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Here.
هنا.
Two men and five women.
رجلين وخمس نساء.
They moved here a few nights ago.
لقد انتقلوا إلى هنا قبل بضع ليال.
Knock.
طرق.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Me, Mr. Five.
أنا ، السيد فايف.
Mr. Five, what do you mean?
السيد خمسة ماذا تقصد؟
You again?
انت مرة اخرى؟
You've hit me.
لقد ضربتني.
We are all gangsters.
كلنا رجال عصابات.
We've been hiding out here.
كنا نختبئ هنا.
Don't bully us too much.
لا ترهبنا كثيرا.
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Who?
من؟
Zhou Qian.
تشو تشيان.
That’s my sister. What do you want?
هذه اختي.  ماذا تريد؟
Call her out.
اتصل بها.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Who let you out?
من تركك تخرج؟
I’m here.
أنا هنا.
Are you Zhou Qian?
هل أنت تشو تشيان؟
Yes.
نعم.
I need to talk to you.
أحتاج لأن أتحدث إليك.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Be good. I won't do anything to you.
كن جيد.  لن أفعل لك أي شيء.
-Mr. Five, you... -Stay out of it.
-السيد.  خمسة ، أنت ... ابق خارجًا.
He's crazy.
انه مجنون.
I didn't dare to mess with him, but you did.
لم أجرؤ على العبث معه ، لكنك فعلت.
Don't blame me for not persuading you.
لا تلومني لعدم إقناعي.
I want to talk to you about Chen.
أريد أن أتحدث إليكم عن تشين.
I've returned
لقد عدت
all his things.
كل ما لديه.
To be honest,
صدقا،
I've exchanged them for money.
لقد استبدلتهم بالمال.
But I didn't ask
لكني لم أسأل
from him.
منه.
He forced me to take them.
أجبرني على أخذهم.
I already handed in the money.
لقد سلمت بالفعل المال.
I paid him back my part.
دفعت له الجزء الخاص بي.
I told him that
أخبرته بذلك
we all work for others.
كلنا نعمل من أجل الآخرين.
I won't contact him anymore.
لن أتصل به بعد الآن.
I won't contact him again.
لن أتصل به مرة أخرى.
I definitely won't contact him again.
بالتأكيد لن أتصل به مرة أخرى.
It's not about money.
الأمر لا يتعلق بالمال.
It's not illegal, is it?
هذا ليس غير قانوني ، أليس كذلك؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
No, I really didn't break the law.
لا ، أنا حقًا لم أخالف القانون.
The matchmaking agency
وكالة التوفيق
asked us to provide information and meet the customers.
طلب منا تقديم المعلومات ومقابلة العملاء.
How much do you get for each customer?
كم تحصل على كل عميل؟
Some customers
بعض العملاء
are handsy.
مفيدون.
You have to...
عليك أن...
You have to find someone to stop him.
عليك أن تجد شخصًا ما لإيقافه.
How much?
كم الثمن؟
About 2,000.
حوالي 2000.
Two thousand.
ألفين.
You live in Lizhou City, Xixia Town, Rui Tan Street,
أنت تعيش في مدينة Lizhou ، مدينة Xixia ، شارع Rui Tan ،
Unit No.2, Street No.3, No.52.
وحدة رقم 2 شارع 3 رقم 52.
You have a younger brother.
لديك أخ أصغر.
Your father works outside.
والدك يعمل بالخارج.
Your mother brought you up.
والدتك أحضرتك.
Right?
حق؟
W-What do you mean?
لم يذكر اسمه: W ماذا تقصد؟
I won't make things difficult for you.
لن أجعل الأمور صعبة عليك.
What do you think of Chen?
ما رأيك في تشين؟
I think he's nice.
أعتقد أنه لطيف.
I really think he is.
أنا حقا أعتقد أنه كذلك.
He never fools around with me.
لم يخدعني أبدًا.
He doesn't even talk nonsense when he's drunk.
إنه لا يتحدث حتى عن الهراء عندما يكون في حالة سكر.
Even our sisters
حتى أخواتنا
like him very much.
أحبه كثيرا.
Do you like him?
هل يعجبك؟
I...
أنا...
People like him
الناس يحبونه
is just playing with us.
يلعب معنا فقط.
He's from the city.
إنه من المدينة.
He has a car and he's rich.
لديه سيارة وهو ثري.
Why did he come to a matchmaking agency to meet a girl?
لماذا جاء إلى وكالة زواج للقاء فتاة؟
How would he know you if he didn't go to the agency?
كيف سيعرفك إذا لم يذهب إلى الوكالة؟
We grew up together.
نشأنا معا.
He has a blood disease.
لديه مرض في الدم.
He can't get married with that disease.
لا يمكنه الزواج بهذا المرض.
So he has never
لذلك لم يفعل ذلك أبدًا
been in a relationship.
كانت في علاقة.
You were the first one.
كنت الاول
But you lied to him.
لكنك كذبت عليه.
Right?
حق؟
Let's get down to business.
دعونا ننكب على العمل.
You earn 2,000 yuan a month.
تكسب 2000 يوان في الشهر.
I'll give you 10,000 yuan a month.
سأعطيك 10000 يوان في الشهر.
You just date Chen.
أنت تواعد تشين.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I date him. You give me money.
أنا أواعده.  تستطيع أن تعطيني المال.
Yes.
نعم.
I pay you to date him.
أنا أدفع لك حتى الآن.
Go shopping, watch movies and have meals with him.
اذهب للتسوق وشاهد الأفلام وتناول وجبات الطعام معه.
Entertain him.
ترفيه عنه.
You're good at
أنت جيد في
these lovey-dovey things.
هذه الأشياء المحببة.
Don't think you need me to teach you.
لا تعتقد أنك بحاجة لي لأعلمك.
You must also dress
يجب عليك أيضا ارتداء الملابس
according to Chen's preference.
حسب تفضيل تشين.
I'll pay for all expenses incurred.
سأدفع جميع النفقات المتكبدة.
If you think it's okay,
إذا كنت تعتقد أنه بخير ،
I'll prepare a contract.
سأقوم بإعداد عقد.
Just sign it.
فقط وقعه.
It's settled then.
تم تسويتها بعد ذلك.
Chen is a good man.
تشين رجل طيب.
He won't bully you either.
لن يتنمر عليك أيضًا.
You don't have to worry
لا داعي للقلق
what he will do to you.
ماذا سيفعل بك.
If you agree,
إذا وافقت،
I can pay you some money first.
يمكنني أن أدفع لك بعض المال أولاً.
What if I don't agree?
ماذا لو لم أوافق؟
Do you know what you do for a living?
هل تعرف ماذا تفعل من أجل لقمة العيش؟
-You’re a liar. -Are you threatening me?
-أنت كاذب.  -هل تهددنى؟
I want 20,000.
اريد 20000.
20,000?
20000؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's a deal.
هذا اتفاق.
Will he agree?
هل يوافق؟
Chen still likes you.
تشن لا يزال يحبك.
Otherwise, how could you
وإلا كيف يمكنك
scam money from him before?
احتيال المال منه من قبل؟
You can rest assured about that.
يمكنك أن تطمئن إلى ذلك.
Any other requirements from your side?
أي متطلبات أخرى من جانبك؟
Don't let him know that I hire you.
لا تدعه يعرف أنني أوظفك.
Be nice to him.
كن لطيفا معه.
I want him to be happy.
أريد له أن يكون سعيدا.
Let me introduce her formally to you.
اسمحوا لي أن أقدمها لك رسميا.
My girlfriend, Zhou Qian.
صديقتي ، تشو تشيان.
Zhou Qian.
تشو تشيان.
This is the boss of our company
هذا هو رئيس شركتنا
who I always mention to you.
الذي أذكره لك دائما.
She is also my childhood friend.
وهي أيضًا صديقة طفولتي.
Xu Banxia.
شو بانكسيا.
Hello, Miss Xu.
مرحبا انسة شو.
Why are you calling her Miss Xu?
لماذا تتصل بها الآنسة شو؟
She's not your boss.
إنها ليست رئيسك في العمل.
Just call her Fatty same with me.
فقط اتصل بها الدهنية معي.
She was very fat when she was young.
كانت سمينة جدا عندما كانت صغيرة.
You can call me whatever you want. Don't listen to him.
يمكنك الاتصال بي ما تريد.  لا تستمع إليه.
By the way,
على فكرة،
this is Mr. Zhao from our company.
هذا هو السيد تشاو من شركتنا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hello, Mr. Zhao.
مرحبا سيد تشاو.
Today,
اليوم،
I gather you here
أجمعك هنا
for one reason.
لسبب واحد.
Today is the 99th day
اليوم هو اليوم التاسع والتسعون
that I have known Zhou Qian.
الذي عرفته Zhou Qian.
You remember it so clearly.
تتذكرها بوضوح.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.